Nicklas Hansen

Github: nicklashansen | LinkedIn: ncklas

[(+45) 61 26 46 82 | M hello@nicklashansen.com | ♠ nicklashansen.com | ♣ 23 | ↑ Copenhagen, Denmark

Research interest

I am highly interested in research on the generalization and robustness of deep reinforcement learning agents, particularly in connection with self-supervision, transfer learning and optimization.

I strive to make artificial intelligence available to a broader audience through research and open source projects.

Education

University of California, Berkeley

Berkeley, CA

Visiting Graduate Student

Spring 2020

A semester devoted to special topics in deep learning and data-driven innovation.

Participant in Innovation Centre Denmark's SPARK program and recipient of the Spar Nord Foundation Scholarship.

Technical University of Denmark

Kongens Lyngby, Denmark

M.Sc. Mathematical Modelling & Computing GPA: 10.5 (-3 to 12)

Feb 2019 -

Largely focused on special topics in deep learning such as deep reinforcement learning, deep unsupervised learning, optimization for deep learning and research on novel applications of deep learning.

Technical University of Denmark

Kongens Lyngby, Denmark

B.Sc. Software Engineering GPA: 8.2 (-3 to 12)

Sep 2015 - Dec 2018

Courses in computer science, statistics, machine learning, AI and project management.

Nanyang Technological University

Singapore

Exchange Student

Fall 2017

Courses in computer vision, cryptology and large-scale software engineering.

Professional experience

Technical University of Denmark

Kongens Lyngby, Denmark

Teaching Assistant

Fall 2019

02456 Deep Learning & 02454 Introduction to Cognitive Science

I taught 6 hours a week, developed course material, corrected assignments and supervised 50+ students' projects on the topics of deep reinforcement learning and self-supervised learning.

Retune DSP

Kongens Lyngby, Denmark

Assistant Software Developer

Feb 2019 - Dec 2019

I help a team of engineers build and maintain deep learning pipelines for embedded voice control systems.

Raffle.ai

Copenhagen, Denmark

Machine Learning Intern

Summer 2019

I reimplemented the SyntaxSQLNet cross-domain text-to-SQL parser in PyTorch and improved its accuracy by 12%. https://github.com/raffle-interns/SyntaxSQLNet

Nordic Transition

Gentofte, Denmark

Lead Software Developer

Jul 2017 - Dec 2019

I developed and maintained a GDPR-compliant data management and analysis platform for the HR industry.